RG 062:044, Town of East Haven
Connecticut State Library
Town of East Haven records
1862-1956
Connecticut State Library
East Haven (Conn.)
15.25 cubic feet
Military records and tax records for the town of East Haven.
RG062_044
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of East Haven was incorporated in May 1785 and was taken from New Haven.
Scope and Content
Military records and tax records for the town of East Haven.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- East Haven -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- East Haven -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- East Haven -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- East Haven -- Registers; Soldiers -- Connecticut -- East Haven
Places:
East Haven (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Document Types:
Military records; Tax records
Restrictions on Access
Military discharges, 1898-1956, Accession 2012-046, 1 envelope, is restricted. Connecticut General Statutes §1-219 restricts veteran’s military records including but not limited to a DD 214 form for 75 years. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1862-1956
  - Military records, 1898-1956; 2012-046
    - Military discharges, 1898-1956; bulk 1917-1956; 1 folder (Box Envelope 1)
      RESTRICTED
      Connecticut General Statutes §1-219 restricts veteran’s military records including but not limited to a DD 214 form for 75 years. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
  - Tax abstracts, 1862-1952; 1998-042; 58 volumes
    Box 6 is on oversize shelving.
    - 1862, 1866, 1867, 1868, 1869 (Box Box 1)
    - 1870, 1871, 1872, 1873, 1874, 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879 (Box Box 2)
    - 1880, 1881, 1884, 1886, 1887, 1888, 1890, 1891, 1892, 1893, 1894-1895, 1896-1897, 1898-1899 (Box Box 3)
    - 1900-1901, 1902, 1903, 1904, 1905, 1906, 1907, 1908, 1909, 1910 (Box Box 4)
    - 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914 (Box Box 5)
    - 1915, 1916 (Box Box 6)
    - 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920 (Box Box 7)
    - 1921, 1922, 1923 (Box Box 8)
    - 1936, 1 volume
    - 1937, 1 volume
    - 1938, 1 volume
    - 1939-1941, 1 volume
      Spine reads 1938-1941.
    - 1942-1944, 1 volume
    - 1945-1946, 1 volume
    - 1952, 1 volume